噢，亲爱的，
Oh. Oh honey
你看Ben留下了什么，还有这花。
look! Ben's punishment letter and flowers too.
哪个Ben。
Ben who?
你醒醒。
Wake up!
Maggie，早上好。
Oh, hello Maggie.
好。
Hello.
早上好。
Good morning.
瞧
look.
Aw.
亲爱的爸爸妈妈，
"Dear Mom and Dad,
这是你们让我写的检讨，
here's my punishment you wanted.
希望你们满意。
I hope you like it.
你们的Ben。
Love Ben.
哦。
Oh.
我还不知道色情两个字我究竟写对了没有。
"I don't know if I spelled pornography right or not."
写对了吗？
Did he?
写对了。
He did.
这是我担心的事。
I was afraid of that.
爸爸，你要我把一切都写下来，
"Dad, you wanted me to write all this stuff down,
写我们是怎么样到这个地步的和我的想法，
and to tell how we got to where we are and what I think about
我做的事情以及为什么说是要不得的。
what I did and why it's disgusting.
(Jason and Maggie reading the letter in their heads).
哦，对不起，你读吧。
Oh sorry.
对我来说，真正的麻烦是昨天，
"For me the real trouble started yesterday
你结账的时候开始的。
when you were paying the bills."
妈妈说得对，
Mom's right.
你一坐下结账准不会有什么好事。
Nothing good can happen when you sit down to pay the bills.
我当时想，尽量不要在旁边听
I was trying to make sure I wasn't around to hear
那些你总是在付账单时说的话
any of those words you always say on bill paying day,
那些话，我是不该听的。
that I'm not supposed to hear.
Hi Ben!
HI，Ben。
嘘……爸爸他在结账！
Shhh. It's bill paying day.
Carol，美发一次就要花掉55美元，
Carol! Fifty five Dollars for a hair-styling
这个该死的美发厅也太昂贵了！
from "Blood, Sweat and Shears", come on!!
他怎么知道我在家的？
How'd he know I was home?
是特异功能。
I know it's weird.
Carol？这可是55！
Carol! Fifty five Dollars!
这事妈妈知道，
Well Mom knew about it.
她说我该去做头发，因为，
She said I should go ahead and get it done because...
我长大了。
I'm blossoming.
你就别说了。
Well stop!
Ben，你对你姐姐说说吧，
Ben will you pleas explain to your sister
你每星期拿到四块钱该有多么的满足。
how you can have a rich and full life on four Bucks a week.
在和我说？
Are you talkin' to me?
你们好。
Hey guys.
你别走开迈克。
And don't you go far Mike,
呆会我有话和你说。
I'm gonna wanna talk to you!
是我闯祸了？
What did I do?
暂时还没有发现。
I haven't found it yet!
怎么回事？
What's going on?
今天是他结账的日子。
It's bill paying day.
我简直不能相信！
Oh, I don't believe this one!!
都给我回来！一个月的电话费就要216美元！
Halt!! Two hundred and sixteen Dollars for a one month phone bill.
太多了？
Is that high?
是的，迈克。
Ok Mike!
67次收费电话都是同一个号码
Sixty seven toll charges, all of the same number,
每次打的都是两美元！
at two Dollars a piece!
每次都是两美元？
Two Dollars a piece?
叫人吃惊对吗？Ben。
Shocking, isn't it Ben?
你干嘛要武断地认为是我？
Look, you know, why do you always automatically assume it's me?
难道家里只有我一个人干错事？
As if I'm the only guy in this house who does anything wrong!
是的
Oh No!
我现在就来拨这个电话
Tell you what Mike, I'm gonna call this number,
来接电话的肯定是个女的。
and I'll just bet you that a girl answers!
那准错不了。
I'm sure of it.
就连十岁的娃娃也看透你了！
Even a ten year old can see through you!
噢。
Oh oh.
-= Subripped by Susie Shi =-       2007.07.22
对不起，在我被粗野地打断之前讲到哪了？
Anyway where was I before I was so rudely interrupted?
哦，对了，爸爸在拨那个电话号码。
Oh yeah, Dad you were dialing that phone number.
我真是吓坏了。但愿听筒里是忙音。
I was so scared, all I could hope for was a busy signal.
喂，我是……对方是录音。
Hello, this is....it's a recording.
性感幻想！
Sexual fantasies?!
是？
Yeah?!
对，迈克！
Yeah, Mike!
真是太恶心了。
Oh! How gross!!
来办公室，咱俩谈谈！
You get in my office. We're gonna talk!
要去大家都去，
Yeah well I think everyone should get in your office,
因为我什么事都没有干！
'cause I didn't do anything!
好吧！你先去办公室
Well then, why don't you get in my office,
他们跟着去办公室
then we'll all come in my office,
咱们大家全都到办公室去。
and we'll deduce who the culprit is!!
这样做也太不公平了！
This is so unfair.
她并不知道怎么个不公平。
She didn't know how unfair.
HI，亲爱的，我回来了。
Hi honey! I'm home.
你来听听吧。
Listen to this.
噢，Jason。
Errm...Jason.
咱们家有个孩子专门打这个号码！
One of our kids has been calling this number!
什么？！
What??
看来妈妈也不能忍受了。
Mom was a teeny bit upset.
唉呀！
Yuk!!
这样的电话一个月打了67次！
Sixty seven times in one month!
是迈克！
Mike!!
可是他否认了！
Oh he denies it!
这样的电话他当然不会承认。
Oh, if he listened to this with Ben around, I'll....
我要尽量地保持冷静
I'm gonna have to be very calm
千万不能冲动。
and very rational about this.
那很好。
Good idea.
知道我要怎么样对付？
You know what I'm gonna do?
帮迈克买一辆车！
I'm gonna buy Mike a new car.
什么？
What?
对！让他看一眼以后
Yeah. Then I'm gonna make him look at it.
我再把它收回来
Then I'm gonna take it away from him,
放在咱们家的草坪上让他烂掉！
I'm gonna park it on the front lawn and let it rust!!
给我听着，是哪个小鬼干的好事？！
Alright! Now which one of you little weasels did this?
算了，迈克，你去表演给爸爸妈妈看吧！
Come on Mike. Save your outraged act for Mom and Dad.
我郑重告诉你，这不是我干的！
Look! I'm telling you I didn't do it!
噢，我明白了，你是想指责--
Oh what? So now you're gonna try and blame.....
小Ben！
little Ben.
对，就是Ben。
Oh, sure, right, Ben.
反正肯定不是我。
Well it certainly wasn't me.
可不管怎么说也逃不了咱们仨。
Well it had to be somebody in this room.
迈克！先假定不是你干的
Mike, just pretend you aren't you. Now...
先用排除嫌疑法来分析
using the process of elimination,
你认为这会是谁干的呢？
who would you say the pervert is?
Ben？Carol？或者迈克？
Ben, Carol, or Mike.
可能吗？不，我先否定你的假设。
Well...no, no I don't wanna pretend that!
我只知道我没干这种事。
All I know is, I didn't do it!
我更不可能干这种事。
And I also know, I didn't.
也许有人溜进来干的？
Hey! Maybe a guy broke in and did it.
溜进来67次？
Sixty seven times!!
迈克，我把话说在前头。
Alright Mike, here's the deal.
要是你承认了
You admit what you did,
你只要等一年就能拿到驾驶执照。
and you only have to wait an extra year for your driver's license;
要是以后承认，只要你在这住你就别想拿到！
you confess later and you won't get it for as long as you live here.
OH，妈妈！
Mom!
给你三十秒钟时间考虑，迈克！
You have thirty seconds to make up your mind Mike.
现在迈克也遇到麻烦了
Now Mike was in trouble too...
真正的麻烦。
real trouble.
这全都是我不好
And it was all my fault.
我不能让他受这个罪
I couldn't let this happen to him,
尽管他常把我当成一个破铅桶看待。
even if he always does treat me like a sleazy bucket.
你说，准备怎么样迈克？
So, what do you have to say Mike?
如果只有两个选择……
Well if those are my only two choices...
迈克？
Mike!
那好吧，是我干的。
Ok then, I did it!
不，是我干的。
No! I did.
小Ben！
Benny!
是你？！
You?
我又不知道这是错的。
I didn't know it was wrong.
这破铅桶的话你们信吗？
Can you believe this little sleazy bucket?
Ben，不管迈克给你多少钱要你承认……
Ben, I don't care how much Mike is paying you to say this...
喂！
Hey!!
没给钱，是我自己干的。
Nothing! I did do it!
Ben，你的动机是想保护迈克，
Honey, it's sweet that you want to protect Mike,
可是你不应该这么做。
but this is not the way to do it.
瞧，
Hey, hey, hey look.
有一个电话是10月20号打的。
It says that one of those calls was made on October twentieth.
这不可能是我打的，
Now, I couldn't have done that 'cause that's the day me
那天我和波拿旷课去柯尼岛了。
and Boner cut class to go to Coney Island.
你逃学了？！
You cut school?
噢！
Uh-oh!
这下子他们该相信了！
That was the convincer.
大部分电话都是在迈克放学前打的。
These calls were all made before Mike even gets back from school.
对，我认为现在应该赔礼道歉了。
Right! I believe an apology is in order here.
Carol，迈克，请你们离开这。
Carol! Mike! You can leave the room please.
我接受道歉，谢谢。
Apology accepted Dad, thank you.
柯尼岛的事我回头再找你。
We'll talk about Coney Island later.
越晚越好。
Later's good.
我这才感到事态有多么的严重
I started to know how serious it was,
他们这样看着我，好像我是个
when you looked at me like I was
失足儿童。
Emmanuel Lewis.
OH，Ben，怎么会是你？！
Ah Benny, not you!
你对这种货色不感兴趣
You're not interested in this kind of stuff.
干嘛要打这种电话？
Why would you call that number?
因为学校里大家都在传这个号码。
Well, this kid at school was passing it around.
让我猜着了。
I knew it!
是谁传给你的？
What's the boy's name?
爸爸，我不能连累任何人。
Dad, I can't rattle on somebody.
这不是连累
Well, you're not ratting on him Ben,
传的人已经错了
this is a kid with a problem.
错了就应该纠正。
He's got to be straightened out.
你想帮他的忙？
Now you'd be doing him favour.
这事能不能不提了。
Can't we just forget about it?
不！是福特曼他们家的孩子？
No! Is it the Futterman boy?
不。
No.
沙利文？
Stinky Sullivan?
嗯。
Uh uh.
你不说出他是谁就别想出这个房间！
Ben, we're not going anywhere until you tell us who it is?
快说Ben，
Tell us Ben.
我们在等着呢，本。
We're waiting Ben.
究竟是谁。
Who is it?
说吧，Ben。
Now Ben!
克里斯库斯曼。
Chris Cussman.
是隔壁？
From next door?
原来是那个小坏蛋！
Why that little dirt-bag!!
Maggie.
对不起，我不是说坏蛋。我说的是……
I'm sorry, I didn't mean to say "dirt-bag", I meant to....
Ben，你说出来是对的
You did...you did the right thing by telling us;
我要减轻对你的惩罚。
that'll make your punishment easier.
Jason，这不是他的错。
Well Jason, it wasn't his fault.
从现在起，你别跟克里斯玩。
Well for now, I don't want you playing with Chris.
可他是我最好的朋友。
But he's my best friend.
不再是了。查查库斯曼家电话号码。
Na, not any more. What's the Cussman's number Maggie?
你不需要这样的朋友。
You don't need friends like that!
以前，凡是能交的朋友我都需要。
Right then, I needed any kind of friend I could find.
我干了那个事
Now I did it.
虽然不是有意，但毕竟是我干的。
I didn't mean to, but I did it.
事情越弄越糟了
I made it worse.
我不仅连累了我最好的朋友
Not only did I rat on my best friend,
而且连累的还是一个无辜的朋友。
I ratted on a friend who was innocent.
我还是去找上帝算了。
I decided to go straight to God.
上帝？（雷声）
God! (thunder)
要是不让你麻烦的话
It won't mess up the world or anything.
能不能让时间倒转一个月
Maybe you could turn time back a month.
短短的一个月。
Just one little month.
HI，Ben，想打一会球吗？
Hi Ben! Wanna play Dodge Ball?
HI，克里斯，我不能。
Err, hi Chris. I Can't.
我爸爸说下周末在船上度假请你来。
My dad says it's alright for you to come on the boat this next weekend.
我也不能去了。
I'm sorry, I can't do that either.
怎么回事？
How come?
我……
Well I...
克里斯·库斯曼
Christian Daniel Cussman!!!!
你给我马上滚回来，小子！
You get your tail back home, right now young man!
是，长官。我什么也没干。
Yes sir! I didn't do anything.
打电话好玩对吗？
Having fun with the phone huh?
你说什么？
What do you mean?
回家！
Hey, we're gonna have to go in the house,
咱们现在得坐下来好好谈谈，
sit down, and you and I are gonna have a little talk young man!!
这样下去，你以后再也坐不下来了。
And then you ain't gonna be able to sit down any more!!
可是爸爸……
But Dad!!!
快进屋去，快！
In the house, now!!
爸爸，我本来可以有别的说法救Chris，
Dad, I could have something right then to save Chris,
可我陷害了。
but I didn't.
这都是因为我不能告诉你和妈妈
All because I couldn't tell you and Mom
是谁把电话号码传给我的。
that the kid who was passing out the number at school,
那个对我有坏影响的人，就是……
the kid who was the bad influence on me, was...
我
me.
我等离家出走了。
I knew I had to get out,
免得你们发现我比迈克更坏。
before you found out that I was even worse than Mike.
再见房间，再见床
Bye room, bye bed,
再见椅背上的脸。
bye chair with the face on it.
我也不知道我要去哪
I didn't know where I was going.
反正是个没电话的地方
Just some place with no phones...
多半是苏联吧。
probably Russia.
（电话响）
(phone rings)
我来接。
I'll get it.
你接。
You got it?
我接。
I got it.
那好。
Good.
喂？对，是的。
Hello. Yes it is.
克瓦斯维其太太
Ah Mrs. Kavasavich,
这么晚还没睡？
you're working late.
校长的工作真是没个完。
Principal's job is never done, is it?
Ben又有什么麻烦了。
Ah, what kind of trouble could Ben be in?
对，电话账单的事我们非常不安。
Yes, we saw the phone bills...
我们已经告诉库斯曼家了。
Tell her we called the Cussmans.
全体家长都发怒了？
All the parents are angry?
恐怕库斯曼的儿子把号码全都传遍了吧。
Well I guess the Cussman boy spread the number to everyone.
什么意思？问我是什么意思？
What do you mean? What do you mean, "what do I mean"?
她什么意思？
What does she mean?
是Ben传的？
Ben did it!?!
什么？
Oh, what?
肯定搞错了
No, there must be some mistake.
Ben告诉我说是克里斯告诉他号码的。
Ben told us he got the number from the Cussman boy.
那小子是个小坏蛋。
Tell her, he's the dirt-bag.
是的，他是个小坏……对，是坏影响。
Yes, he's the dirt....he's the bad influence.
Ben的话和其他同学的对不起来，
Well so it's Ben's word against some other child's...
一共有十四个同学
fourteen other child's?
都说是Ben？
They're all named Ben.
Ben?
Ben？
我不知道说什么才好，
I don't know what to say, I...
我们来处理吧。
oh, we'll handle it.
谢谢你。
Yes thank you.
她肯定吗？
She's sure?
非常肯定。
Very!
这么说Ben是……
Then Ben is the...
小坏蛋！
Dirt-bag!
Jason，我敢说Ben一定是有他的理由
Jason, I'm sure Benny had a very good reason
去打这些电话
for placing those calls.
对，他责怪他的好朋友
Yes, and for blaming his best friend,
可以对我们说谎，还把号码
for lying to us, and for spreading that number
传遍整个小学。
all over Wendell Wilkie Elementary School
好了。你就不能允许一个母亲
Ok. Ok, can't you give a mother just a moment
保护她的孩子一小会吗？
of protecting her young?
如果我们说库斯曼家的孩子的话
Now, either everything we said about Chris Cussman,
都适用于Ben，不然咱们就是伪君子。
now applies to Ben, or we're hypocrites.
我宁可是伪君子。
I vote hypocrite.
Maggie!
Maggie
请你不要再说了。
Good, it's settled.
行了！
Oh, come on!
很抱歉，Jason。
Oh, I'm sorry Jason.
我很难接受那些说Ben传播……
It's just tough for me to accept that Ben is a
黄色毒素的不实之词！
purveyor of pornography.
完了，一切都露底了
Well, the news was out.
这下我要臭名远扬了。
Now it was time to face the music.
听说你把那个下流号码辛苦地
It seems you've been very busy,
传遍了整个学校？
passing a dirty number around school.
这还不算辛苦。
Not that busy.
Ben，你怎么能站在那里
Ben, how could you stand there,
面不改色公然撒谎呢？
stare us straight in the eye, and lie to us?
可我没有说谎。但我说的都是真话。
But I didn't lie, I wanted it to be true.
（门铃）
(door bell)
Ben，你让我感到太失望了。
Ben, I am very disappointed in you.
妈妈从没对我说过这样的话，
Mom had never said that to me before,
看来情况已经越来越糟了，
things were about as bad as they could get;
简直是糟透了。
then they got worse.
库斯曼，老朋友，真高兴你……
Bud Cussman. Oh, am I glad to see you!
大夫，克里斯他有话要说……
Doc, Chris here has something to say.
我们也有话
Well, err, so do we.
请坐。
Come in. Come in.
我从没见过克里斯这么生我的气
I had never seen Chris so mad at me before...
他连走路的样子都变了。
and he was walking kind of funny.
说吧。
Speak!
那好。是这么回事。
Well what happened was...
不是你说，他说。
Not you! Him!
我说，我很抱歉。
Erm, yeah. I'm sorry.
该说非常抱歉。非常抱歉，我把那个号码传给了Ben。
I'm very sorry I gave Ben the dirty phone number...
允许我插上一句……
Now, I have to interrupt here...
不不……你已经在电话里都说了
Oh no no no no Doc, you said it all on phone,
你说克里斯是在
when you said that Chris here
给同伴施加消极的影响。
was...exerting negative peer pressure.
那时我并不知道……
I didn't know...
我也是在调查后才知道……
Me neither until I looked it up!
说吧，小子。
Go ahead Mister.
我要用我的月规钱
And I'll pay for your phone bill out of my allowance
把你们的电话账付清。
until it's all paid off.
好吧，咱们走。
Ok, let's go.
不，请你们等一下，这里有个错误。
Ah wait a minute Bud, there's been a mistake.
错误是什么？
What do you mean a mistake?
现在只有来一场自然灾害才能够救我
All that could save me now was a natural disaster.
下洪水，暴雨，龙卷风什么的。
Like a flood, or a hurricane, or a tycoon.
请你们坐下。
Please Bud sit.
克里斯？
Chris.
我还是站一会吧。
Oww! Maybe later.
我不该给你打电话。
Bud, I should not have called you.
别开玩笑。
Are you kidding.
要是你的孩子干这种事
If it was your kid pulling that malarkey,
我会来拼命拍你的门
I'd be knocking at your door looking to
找给同伴施加消极影响的人算账。
exert negative peer pressure on somebody's face.
嗯？
Ah ha?
这样看来
You know Doc. under the circumstances,
你称得上是位货真价实的君子。
I think you're being a real gentleman.
我希望你尽量发挥你的讽刺才能。
Bud, I'd like to appeal to your sense of irony here.
好吧。
Ok.
说起来
Well you know,
这件事实在有点滑稽。
when you think about it, it's almost kind of funny.
滑稽？
Funny?
我是个精神病学家，
Well see as a psychiatrist,
我知道儿童陷入困境时常常会晕头转向。
I understand that a kid can get confused when he gets in a jam.
我是水管工。
Well as a plumber, I know that
但孩子瞒我什么，
when my kid stops up on me.
我会有办法让他畅通的。
I gotta flush the truth out of him.
我再也受不了，我也垮了。
I couldn't take it any more! I cracked.
是我干的，库斯曼先生，
I did it Mr. Cussman, I did it!
我传的我传了那个电话号码。
I passed out the number!
你对我说谎？！
You lied to me!
我说过，我对你对说不是我干的。
I told you it wasn't me Pop!
把你的皮烤黑以后
Yeah but then after I tanned your hide,
你还说是你干的？
you said it was.
这一切我感到很抱歉，真的。
We're just very sorry about the whole thing, really.
好了，别道歉了，
Ah, It's no sweat.
他这顿屁股是不是白打了，
Little buckaroo probably had a spankin' comin' for
这也很难说。
something I didn't even know about.
可是爸爸……
But Pop I...
听我来，我来弥补，
Look look look. Tell you what I'm gonna do.
下次该打板子的时候就免了，
Next time you got a couple of whacks coming,
因为你预支了。好，走吧。
I'll forget about it. Hah? Come on.
请等一下，这个例子就生动地说明……
Now you see, this is a perfect example of how I,
说明我本人，就该--防止对孩子匆忙地做出任何结论。
for one, have learnt not to jump to conclusions about my children.
你说得对，咱们走吧。
I don't blame you. Come on let's go.
Ben，你对克里斯有什么要说的？
Ben, don't you have something to say to Chris.
克里斯？
Chris!
什么？
What?
我很抱歉。
I'm sorry.
你也太没礼貌了。
Hey! Hey, that's rude!
好吧，那是你的飞碟，去玩去吧。
Right that's your freebie pal, enjoy it!!
真是的，我不知道该拿他怎么办，
Why, I don't know what gets into him, you know.
他的行为，像个幼稚的孩子。
Sometimes he...he acts like a little kid.
好了Ben，我要你到房间里去。
Well Ben, I want you to go to your room.
好好想一想为什么说打那种电话是错的。
I want you to think about why making those phone calls was wrong.
为什么说讲假话是错上加错。
Why lying about them was even more wrong.
你怎么来弥补。
And what you're gonna do about it.
我要呆很久吗？
So I'll be there a long time?
去吧。
Go.
我不知道我呆了多久
I don't know how long I was there
去想你们想听什么
trying to figure out what you wanted to hear.
我一定是睡着了
I must have fell asleep,
因为我突然感到这好像是一场噩梦。
'cause it suddenly came to me that it was all a bad dream,
我从来没打什么电话，
that I never called nobody,
我还是你们心爱的儿子。
and I was the same little kid you loved.
然后Carol进来了。
Then Carol walked in.
Ben!
Ben？
是早上了吗？
Is it morning?
噢，这在澳大利亚是早上，这里不是。
In Australia, but no here.
我要警告你，
Listen, I wanted to warn you,
爸爸正在上楼来要和你谈谈，
Dad's coming up here to talk to you
他一边走，鼻子一边还在出大气。
and he's been walking around breathing through his nose.
天啊！
Oh no.
受严重的惩罚既然你是第一次，
Since this is your first time with the big punishment scene,
我透露给你点秘密。
I thought I'd give you a few tips.
你从没有帮过迈克。
You never helped Mike?!
瞧迈克挨整挺有意思。
Seeing him squirm is fun.
你看上去就像个可怜的小动物在挣扎。
Seeing you suffer is like seeing Merve Griffindon sing.
谢谢你。
Thanks.
你首先得知道，
First thing you have to know,
咱们干了任何坏事，他们都会怪自己不好。
is that parents blame themselves for every bad thing we do.
真的。
Really?
对，首先你走投无路了就说，
Yeah, so if you get cornered, say something like...
我原先并不知道……
"I didn't know any better."
第二，你该说这种念头是从摇滚乐里学来的
Second, say you got the idea from rock music lyrics.
说完了，Carol？
You finished Carol?
爸爸，你来了多久了？
Dad! How long have you been here?
足够久。
Long enough.
Carol说得对，他鼻子是在出大气。
Carol was right, you were breathing through your nose.
Ben，我想……
Ben, I have....
爸爸，我原先并不知道，
Dad, I didn't know any better,
我，再也不听摇滚乐了。
and I'm through with rock and roll.
好过点了吗？
Better?
不。
No!
太失望了。
Nuts.
如果你老实一点，
Ben this is gonna go a lot faster
这个谈话也许可以轻松得多。
if you'll just be straight with me. Ok?
可以。
Ok.
电话号码哪来的？
Where did you get the number?
公园树上的传单上。
From a poster on a tree in the park
是大孩子们张贴的。
where the big kids hang out.
是真话吗？
That's the truth?
对。谈完了吗？
Yes. Are we done?
没有。我要让你知道。
No. I'll let you know.
你明不明白你是在听一些
Did you know that what you were listening to,
你不该听的话吗？
you shouldn't be listening to?
明白一点。
Kind o'.
真的明白吗？
That's yes?
不。
No.
这么说你不明白。
Then you didn't know?
也不能这么说。
Not exactly.
Ben，你就别绕圈子了。
Ben, we were on a roll here.
我知道那是下流的，
Well, I knew it was dirty but,
可我也听不太明白。
it didn't make much sense.
你干嘛到处传号码？
Well then, why did you pass it out?
我到处传？
Are you kidding?
有人说我有号码，
Word spread I had the number,
一下子全来找我了。
and kids were all over me!
就连大孩子也来了。
Even big kids!
我再也不是迈克的小弟弟了，
For once I wasn't Mike's little brother,
我成了大红人Ben了。
I was Ben, the good time guy.
这算是出风头，Ben。
That's a dubious distinction Ben.
对，可挺带劲。
Yeah, it was great.
Ben，要是你对性的问题感到好奇
Look if you're curious about sex
就该来找我和妈妈，
you've gotta come to me or your Mom and talk.
怎么能用手指代替脚走路？
Don't let your fingers do the walking.
我讨厌电话了。
I hate the phone.
从今以后我再也不打电话了。
I'm never gonna use the phone again.
孩子，咱们可以谈谈性的问题。
Well, we have to talk about sex here.
难道我听的还不够吗？
Haven't I heard enough about that?
可是你并没有听到正确的，
Well you haven't heard anything that's right,
健康的，真正的
or healthy, or real.
你所听到的只不过是那种下流电话里
Sex isn't something that you buy or sell on the street,
经过歪曲了的东西。
or at a newsstand, or on the phone.
真的？
Yeah.
对。
Sex is a beautiful thing.
应该说性是一种非常美好的东西，
It's a private thing that two people share
是属于两个人之间的一种私事。
when they care about each other.
绝不是指一个人和公共用品之间的事。
It's not between one person and a public utility.
(Back to present time)
你对他说这些话了？
You actually told him that?
对，差不多是那样。
More or less, yeah.
当我写下你对我说的这些话时，
That's when you told me to write all this stuff down.
我学到了不少东西，
I learnt a lot from this.
我懂得了不该用性问题为自己扬名，
I know that sex isn't something you use to make you famous.
我也懂得了不该打那些电话。
And I know that I never should have made those calls,
我会用自己的钱付帐。
and I'll pay you for them somehow.
我唯一还不明白的就是，
The one thing I still don't get,
既然这类下流货色不该让我这样的人听见，
is since I shouldn't hear junk like that,
那为什么这种号码竟会连小孩也能搞到？
how come it's so easy for a little kid like me to get the number?
真遗憾
Alright, I'm sorry!
这次Ben也做得太过分了点！
Your little Benny has gone too far this time!
怎么回事？
What's this?
他把电话线都藏起来了，
He hid all the phone chords.
说一听就头疼。
Says they only cause heartache.
他这样我看很聪明。
Oh, I think it's kind o' cute.
聪明？
Cute?!?!
我看应该好好教训他。
Now he has got to be punished.
你们应该硬起心肠来惩罚他一下。
You know, I think it's time you guys took a firmer hand with him....
你提醒得好。说到惩罚，
Speaking of punishment,
你旷课去柯尼岛的那笔账还跟你算呢！
there's still that little matter of you cutting school to go to Coney Island.
可我想靠惩罚也解决不了问题，
On the other hand, what good does punishment really do?
如今的孩子需要的是爱。
What kids need today is "love."
所以你们应该--
So why not reach out,
伸出双手，抚摸你们的孩子。
reach out, and touch someone.
呵呵，真会随机应变。
You gotta admit it.
很对，他也很聪明。
Yep. He is good.